The next program game is here.
It's boiling water to the tummy.
I don't like something cold.
I'm getting in.
Oh, no, don't do that.
I'm here, just in case.
He's on board.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's being very aggressive.
I don't like it.
Like, he's trying to get me to take one.
That's for sure.
It's like he's speeding up.
He's really aggressive.
I doubt it.
He's been trying to get to one since a while ago.
It's kind of speeding up.
That's good.
Oh, eh.
I'm willing to forgive.
Oh, yeah.
I want to forgive you.
You know, we were all talking today.
You know, we were all talking today about who's the best at lying.
I think I'm the best liar in the world.
What do you think? What do you think?
I think I'm the best liar.
What do you think? Hey, guys.
Let's try them one at a time.
I don't know what to think, but we only have two bottles.
You can't do it.
No, it's impossible.
TRANSD
TRAMPOLA
Half, half
Totally selfless.
Super, awesome
These letters...
No, what is it called?
Throw away the ude
♪ I wanna sing, smile
♪ I'ma be mine
♪ Hear me now, I don't mean nothing
♪ If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
♪ It's up now It's up now
♪ Yuseiso, destiny
I'm going in here. I'm going in here.
I'm going to go for the extreme. - I'm going to go for it.
- We're going for it.
We're going for it. - We're going for it.
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
Yes!
No more words
- No more words.
# No more if it's a word
What's up?
# No more words
Up here?
Up there?
But you know what? One...
Yeah.
# No more words
- Fifty.
It looks like a head, torso and legs.
- You're right.
It's like a pinched mouth.
# If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
Mouth.
I don't want words anymore
What?
# No more words
Ah!
Take it, take it, take it.
Take it.
# If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
- I don't need any more words.
I'm going on the offensive. - I'm going on the offensive. - You sure you want to take him down?
I'll definitely take you down?
- What do you think Yuzu just said? - I doubt it.
- It's suspicious. - It's too deliberate.
- But wouldn't it be funny if we took him down? - It's not crazy. - It's not crazy at all.
- Don't ever knock it over.
Don't let it fall over. - Don't let it fall over. - Don't let it fall over.
I'll make sure it goes down
But won't it be funny if we take it down soon?
I'm gonna keep it down, I'm gonna keep it down
- But wouldn't it be funny if we took it down soon? - Down!
Don't ever take me down.
Don, Chong.
Yup.
Y a l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l l
Y a l l l l l l l l l l
Y a l l l l l l l y
More and more
P la
texto: "Great Apa" for disaster
Y a l l l l l l y
訤 menu
Yes, so the one who defeated
Ichikara-san!
I thought for sure you were going to beat him!
What are you going to do? Who do you want to nominate?
Who do you want to nominate?
Um, well...
Aira, this year?
You just have to guess if Yuzu is real or not.
Gaki or on purpose?
Gaki means he was serious.
Yes, not the joker.
Joker did it on purpose.
This is stiff.
Who do you think is the Joker?
Well, I don't know.
You don't know.
I don't know.
You don't know?
But I'll give it to you.
If he really is the Joker on purpose...
I think he'd try more tricks.
You think?
I don't know.
He's making it seem like he wants to be the only one.
He's trying to make it look like he's on the offensive.
But if he really wanted to be aggressive.
I think he'd attack in a different way.
I see.
That's what I thought.
I'm serious.
I think it's real.
No, it's not.
I think I know what it is.
That's the one.
That's good.
I'm not serious.
I got it. I got it.
You're fine.
I'm good.
Uh...
No, thank you.
All right, everyone.
lake Mulberry intended
job person dive
wear
no
innkeepers
energetic
I do
I don't understand.
Yuzu is the punishment.
But you didn't set anything up.
I did a lot of tricks.
Usually.
No, not really.
On the contrary, you seemed cautious.
That's my move, too.
Mine.
Punishment.
Punishment game. It is boiling water to the stomach.
Yes, so...
Mr. Ichikawa's game of punishment.
I will pour boiling water into your stomach.
I'm counting on you.
I won't show any mercy.
I'll pour it all in.
Not this lame hoodie.
It's not tacky. It's not tacky.
Okay, here we go.
Boiling water. Boiling water in the belly.
From the top?
Don't look at me.
Fuck!
Ehhhh!
It's not good. It's not good.
You say that so often.
You're always asking me to show you.
It's naughty.
Punishment game.
So, can you do that without looking?
Just do the penalty game.
I don't know what that means.
Beige, do this.
I don't understand.
She's always trying to take the lead like this.
You should want to.
He's watching what you say.
I'm sorry.
I snooped, so I'm being punished.
I didn't.
What's that? Punishment?
You're laughing 200% of the time and getting angry.
You can get angry and say you didn't see it.
I didn't see it, even if I did see it.
Because it's 200%,
You are a person who gets angry while laughing hard.
It's funny, isn't it?
I'm really asking you to do it to the max.
Please be angry at Moka.
I'm not on today.
It's fine this way.
Oh no, they'll cut me out again, me.
I can't help it.
It's hard to do.
No one gets angry while laughing 200% of the time.
Three, two, one.
I always feel like I'm getting screwed over.
I feel like a non-taker, and I think about it a lot.
It pisses me off.
I'm depressed.
Punishment game.
Sorry, sorry.
Oh no, wait.
After this, Bunjo.
Not at all, not at all.
Oh, no, don't do this.
I'm not going to do it.
My breasts don't collide.
I was handling it, but I think I can do it.
Why, why, why, why.
I don't feel strange.
Stop it.
I love it. I love it.
Here we go.
Oh, no!
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God.
This thing is going to collapse.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm against it. That's rude.
I can win.
Why don't you just give it all back at once?
I'll take it.
Oh, yeah.